They Really Get Under your Skin
Camel Spiders is a horror, science fiction,
fantasy film directed by Jim Wynorski.
Based on actual creatures that for years have tormented our armed forces in the Middle East,
these creatures have now invaded the southwestern deserts of the United States.
The Camel Spiders now freely hunt for prey,
unafraid of any predator - including man.
No place is safe no one is beyond their paralyzing sting.
In the end, a small band of hearty fighters are forced to
make one last stand against the creatures.
Sturges, played by Brian Krause.
Wendy, played by Paula LaBaredas.
Sheriff Beaumont, played by C. Thomas Howell.
Reba, played by GiGi Erneta.
Patty, played by Diana Terranova.
Sgt. Shelly Underwood, played by Melissa Brasselle.
Camel Spiders is a 2011 made-for-television horror
sci-fi film starring Brian Krause, C.
Thomas Howell, and Jessica Cameron.
It was directed by genre veteran Jim Wynorski and
executive-produced by Roger Corman.
The film explores themes of arizona, spider, giant spider.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking.